What a remarkable moment... The Ten Stonehearts have welcomed their youngest-ever P46.
Aventurine, congratulations on making it into the deep end of the IPC~
Although... wasn't the last P46 the one you personally took out, Opal?
Though, "Aventurine" is synonymous with surprises, no?
Thank you for your kind words...
May we all live up to Diamond's trust in the journey ahead.
First the wiretaps, now the impeachment...
Couldn't wait to roll out the welcome wagon, huh?
Jade was right...
Better have "friends" if you wanna secure a foothold here.
Now then... where should I start looking for you (traitor)?
Oswaldo's schedule is mapped down to the minute he brushes his teeth.
Muddlefudge, what're ya lookin' to trade?
Keep tabs on him. The longer, the better.
Our thanks to the Ten Stonehearts for their support during the battle against Irontomb.
Thanks for providing us with the gravitational wave data.
May we continue to support one another.
Supplies received.
Celenova's Legion has been biding its time of late.
No matter. Just keep me posted if anything comes up.
Mr. Zazzad (Head of the Talent Motivation Department), thank you for providing Agate's files.
You'll have my support at the next cross-department meeting.
Thanks to your generous funding, the Knights are one step closer to the Beauty!
Don't mention it.
But could I ask you to investigate something for me?
What exactly did Opal destroy...
on this planet?
The chips are in the pot...
Now... which card will seal the win?
Oh? Time to cash in.
I've analyzed this dataset based on your markers.
What trick are you pulling this time, Gambler?
With every Lord Ravager at the Irontomb battle,
Archforger finally left a trail.
Come on, let's see if this absurd theory of mine holds up.
Hmph. Pulling data from the Deep Web?
You mean business.
Now, let the game of cat and mouse begin.
Search initiated, matching sequence started...
The Legion: No results.
Architects: No results.
Nomadic Miners: No results.
Marketing Development Department: No results.
Do you wish to continue?
There's still a blind spot.
Warning! Warning!
Match Rate: 99.93%.
The Ten Stonehearts' traitor is the Lord Ravager (Archforger)
aiming for the Preservation?
Looks like the wind's picking up.
Astropolis caught in the storm...
Who will have the last laugh?